[
    [
        {
            "question": "An ideal battery of 4 V and resistance R in a potentiometer gives 5 mV across 10 cm of wire. Then R is:",
            "options": [
                "490",
                "495",
                "395",
                "480"
            ],
            "correctOption": "395",
            "id": 29
        },
        {
            "question": "A solid conducting sphere with charge Q is surrounded by an uncharged conducting hollow shell. If shell is given charge \u20134Q, the new potential difference is:",
            "options": [
                "4 V",
                "V",
                "2 V",
                "\u20132 V"
            ],
            "correctOption": "V",
            "id": 27
        },
        {
            "question": "A car accelerates uniformly from rest and covers a distance of 100 m in 5 s. Its acceleration is:",
            "options": [
                "8 m/s\u00b2",
                "10 m/s\u00b2",
                "5 m/s\u00b2",
                "6 m/s\u00b2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "8 m/s\u00b2",
            "id": 21
        },
        {
            "question": "A body in SHM with 10 cm amplitude is tripled in velocity at 5 cm displacement. New amplitude\u00b2 is:",
            "options": [
                "100",
                "400",
                "700",
                "500"
            ],
            "correctOption": "700",
            "id": 19
        },
        {
            "question": "Two forces A and A/2 are perpendicular. Resultant magnitude is:",
            "options": [
                "(\u221a5)A/2",
                "5A/2",
                "(\u221a5)A\u00b2/2",
                "(\u221a5)A/4"
            ],
            "correctOption": "(\u221a5)A/2",
            "id": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The dimensional formula for pressure is:",
            "options": [
                "ML\u207b\u00b9T\u207b\u00b2",
                "MLT\u207b\u00b2",
                "ML\u00b2T\u207b\u00b2",
                "M\u207b\u00b9L\u207b\u00b9T\u207b\u00b2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "ML\u207b\u00b9T\u207b\u00b2",
            "id": 23
        },
        {
            "question": "Two projectiles A and B are thrown at 40 m/s and 60 m/s at angles 30\u00b0 and 60\u00b0. The ratio of their ranges is:",
            "options": [
                "4 : 9",
                "2 : 3",
                "1 : 1",
                "3 : 2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "4 : 9",
            "id": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Fundamental frequency of a closed pipe = first overtone of open pipe. If open pipe is 60 cm, closed pipe is:",
            "options": [
                "15",
                "20",
                "25",
                "60"
            ],
            "correctOption": "15",
            "id": 16
        },
        {
            "question": "In SHM, if displacement is half amplitude, ratio of PE to KE is:",
            "options": [
                "1:1",
                "1:4",
                "2:1",
                "1:3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1:3",
            "id": 20
        },
        {
            "question": "Average KE of a monatomic molecule is 0.414 eV. Temp is:",
            "options": [
                "3000 K",
                "3200 K",
                "1600 K",
                "1500 K"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3200 K",
            "id": 12
        },
        {
            "question": "AC cannot be measured by DC ammeter because:",
            "options": [
                "A.C cannot pass",
                "A.C changes direction",
                "Avg value is zero",
                "D.C. ammeter gets damaged"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Avg value is zero",
            "id": 44
        },
        {
            "question": "The moment of inertia of a solid sphere about its diameter is:",
            "options": [
                "2/5 MR\u00b2",
                "3/5 MR\u00b2",
                "1/2 MR\u00b2",
                "2/3 MR\u00b2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2/5 MR\u00b2",
            "id": 24
        },
        {
            "question": "Four particles A, B, C, D have same momentum. Which has max kinetic energy?",
            "options": [
                "D",
                "C",
                "A",
                "B"
            ],
            "correctOption": "A",
            "id": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "The energy of a photon is 3.3 \u00d7 10\u207b\u00b9\u2079 J. Its frequency is (Planck's constant h = 6.626 \u00d7 10\u207b\u00b3\u2074 Js):",
            "options": [
                "5 \u00d7 10\u00b9\u2074 Hz",
                "3 \u00d7 10\u2078 Hz",
                "2 \u00d7 10\u00b9\u2074 Hz",
                "1 \u00d7 10\u2079 Hz"
            ],
            "correctOption": "5 \u00d7 10\u00b9\u2074 Hz",
            "id": 50
        },
        {
            "question": "Photoelectric threshold wavelength is 380 nm. With 260 nm, KE is:",
            "options": [
                "1.5 eV",
                "15.1 eV",
                "4.5 eV",
                "3.0 eV"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1.5 eV",
            "id": 38
        },
        {
            "question": "Temp of gas is -78\u00b0C and avg KE is k. Temp for avg KE = 2k is:",
            "options": [
                "117",
                "320",
                "160",
                "-157"
            ],
            "correctOption": "117",
            "id": 13
        },
        {
            "question": "In an LCR series circuit, the resonance frequency is given by:",
            "options": [
                "1/(2\u03c0\u221a(LC))",
                "1/(2\u03c0RC)",
                "1/(2\u03c0LR)",
                "1/(LC)"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1/(2\u03c0\u221a(LC))",
            "id": 48
        },
        {
            "question": "Two equal resistances in series consume 60 W. When in parallel, the power consumed is:",
            "options": [
                "240 W",
                "120 W",
                "60 W",
                "30 W"
            ],
            "correctOption": "240 W",
            "id": 28
        },
        {
            "question": "The speed of light in the medium is:",
            "options": [
                "minimum on the axis of the beam",
                "maximum on the axis of the beam",
                "the same everywhere in the beam",
                "directly proportional to the intensity I"
            ],
            "correctOption": "minimum on the axis of the beam",
            "id": 31
        },
        {
            "question": "Current in coil changes from 5A to 2A in 0.1 s, 50 V induced. Self-inductance is:",
            "options": [
                "0.67 H",
                "1.67 H",
                "3 H",
                "6 H"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1.67 H",
            "id": 42
        },
        {
            "question": "In hydrogen atom transition to ground state:",
            "options": [
                "kinetic energy decreases, potential energy increases but total remains same",
                "kinetic energy increases, potential and total decrease",
                "kinetic and total decrease, potential increases",
                "kinetic, potential and total energy decrease"
            ],
            "correctOption": "kinetic energy increases, potential and total decrease",
            "id": 37
        },
        {
            "question": "For y = sin(\u03c9t) + cos(\u03c9t), the amplitude is:",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "1.414",
                "2",
                "1.5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1.414",
            "id": 17
        },
        {
            "question": "A ball is thrown up at 150 m/s. Ratio of velocity after 3s and 5s is (x+1)/x. Find x:",
            "options": [
                "6",
                "10",
                "\u20135",
                "5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "5",
            "id": 5
        },
        {
            "question": "Heavy nucleus breaks into two. If velocity ratio is 8:27, radius ratio is:",
            "options": [
                "3:2",
                "2:3",
                "4:9",
                "8:27"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3:2",
            "id": 36
        },
        {
            "question": "A capacitor of 9 pF is filled with two dielectrics (k1 = 3, k2 = 6). The new capacitance is:",
            "options": [
                "20.25 pF",
                "1.8 pF",
                "45 pF",
                "40.5 pF"
            ],
            "correctOption": "40.5 pF",
            "id": 30
        },
        {
            "question": "As the beam enters the medium, it will:",
            "options": [
                "travel as a cylindrical beam",
                "converge",
                "diverge",
                "diverge near axis and converge at periphery"
            ],
            "correctOption": "converge",
            "id": 32
        },
        {
            "question": "Two satellites A and B in same orbit. A is twice mass of B. Which is same for both?",
            "options": [
                "Potential energy",
                "Total energy",
                "Kinetic energy",
                "Speed"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Speed",
            "id": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Radioactive source gives 1600 cps at t=0, 100 cps at t=8s. At t=6s it gives:",
            "options": [
                "250",
                "360",
                "150",
                "200"
            ],
            "correctOption": "200",
            "id": 40
        },
        {
            "question": "Red LED emits 0.1W uniformly. Electric field amplitude at 1 m is:",
            "options": [
                "2.45 V/m",
                "7.75 V/m",
                "1.73 V/m",
                "5.48 V/m"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2.45 V/m",
            "id": 43
        },
        {
            "question": "A parallel plate capacitor having capacitance 12 pF is charged by a battery to 10 V. A porcelain slab of dielectric constant 6.5 is inserted. The work done by the capacitor on the slab is:",
            "options": [
                "508 pJ",
                "692 pJ",
                "560 pJ",
                "600 pJ"
            ],
            "correctOption": "508 pJ",
            "id": 26
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "N(CH3)3 and P(CH3)3 can act as ligands. As N and P are from same group, the nature of bonding is always same with transition metals.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
            "id": 9
        },
        {
            "question": "Common name of Benzene - 1,2 - diol is:",
            "options": [
                "o-cresol",
                "catechol",
                "quinol",
                "resorcinol"
            ],
            "correctOption": "catechol",
            "id": 12
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the volume of 1 g of H2 gas in litres at N.T.P",
            "options": [
                "11.2",
                "22.4",
                "2.24",
                "112"
            ],
            "correctOption": "11.2",
            "id": 31
        },
        {
            "question": "Kjeldahl method is applicable to pyridine. The nitrogen in pyridine can be converted to ammonium sulfate.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
            "id": 17
        },
        {
            "question": "Acidity of \u03b1-hydrogens of aldehydes and ketones is responsible for Aldol reaction. Benzaldehyde and ethanal will not give Cross-Aldol product.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
            "id": 19
        },
        {
            "question": "Which compound will not give silver mirror with ammoniacal AgNO3?",
            "options": [
                "Formic acid",
                "Formaldehyde",
                "Benzaldehyde",
                "Acetone"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Acetone",
            "id": 20
        },
        {
            "question": "Coagulation of egg on heating is because of:",
            "options": [
                "Denaturation of protein occurs.",
                "Biological properties of proteins remain unchanged",
                "Breaking of peptide linkage in the primary structure of protein occurs",
                "The secondary structure of protein remains unchanged"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Denaturation of protein occurs.",
            "id": 6
        },
        {
            "question": "Which nitrogen compound does not give Lassaigne's test?",
            "options": [
                "Hydrazine",
                "Urea",
                "Glycene",
                "Phenyl Hydrazine"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Hydrazine",
            "id": 16
        },
        {
            "question": "The vapor pressure of pure benzene and methyl benzene at 27\u00b0C is given as 80 Torr and 24 Torr, respectively. The mole fraction of methyl benzene in vapor phase, in equilibrium with an equimolar mixture of those two liquids is:",
            "options": [
                "0.23",
                "0.89",
                "0.99",
                "0.73"
            ],
            "correctOption": "0.23",
            "id": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Phenol treated with chloroform in presence of sodium hydroxide, then hydrolyzed in acid results in:",
            "options": [
                "2-Hydroxybenzaldehyde",
                "Salicylic Acid",
                "quinol",
                "Benzene-1,2-diol"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2-Hydroxybenzaldehyde",
            "id": 11
        },
        {
            "question": "Fusion of MnO2 with KOH and an oxidising agent gives dark green K2MnO4. Manganate ion on electrolytic oxidation in alkaline medium gives permanganate ion.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE",
            "id": 5
        },
        {
            "question": "The higher oxidation states are more stable down the group among transition elements unlike p-block elements. Copper cannot liberate hydrogen from weak acids.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
            "id": 8
        },
        {
            "question": "The shape of carbocation is:",
            "options": [
                "trigonal planar",
                "tetrahedral",
                "diagonal",
                "linear"
            ],
            "correctOption": "trigonal planar",
            "id": 36
        },
        {
            "question": "The element having the highest first ionization enthalpy is",
            "options": [
                "C",
                "Al",
                "N",
                "Si"
            ],
            "correctOption": "N",
            "id": 39
        },
        {
            "question": "Time required for 99.9% completion of a first order reaction is _________ times the time required for 90% completion.",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "3",
                "9"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "From the following statements regarding H2O2, choose the incorrect statement",
            "options": [
                "It can act only as an oxidizing agent",
                "It has to be stored in plastic or wax-lined glass bottles in the dark",
                "It has to be kept away from dust",
                "It decomposes on exposure to light"
            ],
            "correctOption": "It can act only as an oxidizing agent",
            "id": 26
        },
        {
            "question": "The reaction at cathode in the cells commonly used in clocks involves:",
            "options": [
                "reduction of Mn from +4 to +3",
                "oxidation of Mn from +2 to +7",
                "oxidation of Mn from +3 to +4",
                "reduction of Mn from +7 to +2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "reduction of Mn from +4 to +3",
            "id": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Number of atoms in the following samples of substances is the largest in:",
            "options": [
                "127.0g of iodine",
                "48.0g of magnesium",
                "71.0g of chlorine",
                "4.0g of hydrogen"
            ],
            "correctOption": "4.0g of hydrogen",
            "id": 35
        },
        {
            "question": "p-nitrophenol is more acidic than m- and o-nitrophenol. Ethanol will give immediate turbidity with Lucas reagent.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
            "id": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "\u2206U is equal to",
            "options": [
                "adiabatic work",
                "isothermal work",
                "isochoric work",
                "isobaric work"
            ],
            "correctOption": "adiabatic work",
            "id": 33
        },
        {
            "question": "The incorrect statements regarding enzymes are:",
            "options": [
                "Enzymes are bio catalysts.",
                "Enzymes are non-specific and cannot catalyse different kinds of reactions.",
                "Most enzymes are globular proteins.",
                "Enzyme - oxidase catalyses the hydrolysis of maltose into glucose."
            ],
            "correctOption": "Enzyme - oxidase catalyses the hydrolysis of maltose into glucose.",
            "id": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "The process with negative entropy change is",
            "options": [
                "dissolution of iodine in water",
                "sublimation of dry ice",
                "synthesis of ammonia from N2 and H2",
                "dissociation of CaSO4(s) to CaO(s) and SO3(g)"
            ],
            "correctOption": "synthesis of ammonia from N2 and H2",
            "id": 34
        },
        {
            "question": "The molecular formula of second homologue in the mono carboxylic acids series is:",
            "options": [
                "C2H2O4",
                "C2H2O2",
                "CH2O",
                "C3H6O2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "C2H2O4",
            "id": 18
        },
        {
            "question": "The metal that cannot be obtained by electrolysis of an aqueous solution of its salt is",
            "options": [
                "Cr",
                "Ca",
                "Ag",
                "Cu"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Ca",
            "id": 27
        },
        {
            "question": "Addition of phosphate fertilizers to water bodies causes",
            "options": [
                "enhanced growth of algae",
                "increase in amount of dissolved oxygen in water",
                "deposition of calcium phosphate",
                "increase in fish population"
            ],
            "correctOption": "enhanced growth of algae",
            "id": 28
        },
        {
            "question": "The alkene that exhibits geometrical isomerism is:",
            "options": [
                "2\u2013methyl\u20132\u2013butene",
                "Propene",
                "2\u2013butene",
                "2\u2013methylpropene"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2\u2013butene",
            "id": 24
        },
        {
            "question": "Determine the total number of neutrons in three isotopes of hydrogen",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "3",
                "4"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 29
        },
        {
            "question": "Chlorine water on standing loses its colour and forms:",
            "options": [
                "HCl and HClO2",
                "HCl only",
                "HOCl and HOCl2",
                "HCl and HOCl"
            ],
            "correctOption": "HCl and HOCl",
            "id": 30
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of the following conformation of cyclohexane is chiral?",
            "options": [
                "Twist boat",
                "Rigid",
                "Chair",
                "Boat"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Twist boat",
            "id": 23
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of the following substances has the highest proton affinity?",
            "options": [
                "H2S",
                "NH3",
                "PH3",
                "H2O"
            ],
            "correctOption": "NH3",
            "id": 32
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "If sin A + cos A = \u00bd , then 16(sin(2A) + cos(4A) + sin(6A)) is equal to :",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "-23",
                "35",
                "43"
            ],
            "correctOption": "-23",
            "id": 32
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of integers between 100 and 1000 having the sum of their digits equals to 14 , is _________",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "70",
                "35",
                "43"
            ],
            "correctOption": "70",
            "id": 27
        },
        {
            "question": "Let S = {1, 2, 3, 5, 7, 10, 11}. The number of non-empty subsets of S that have the sum of all elements a multiple of 3, is _____________.",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "20",
                "35",
                "43"
            ],
            "correctOption": "43",
            "id": 45
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of e^0?",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "0",
                "e",
                "-1"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1",
            "id": 9
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the solution to the equation x^2 - 4 = 0?",
            "options": [
                "x = \u00c2\u00b12",
                "x = 2",
                "x = -2",
                "x = 0"
            ],
            "correctOption": "x = \u00c2\u00b12",
            "id": 18
        },
        {
            "question": "The portion of the line 4x+5y=20 in the first quadrant is trisected by the lines P and Q passing through the origin. The tangent of an angle between the lines P and Q is :",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "30/41",
                "35/41",
                "43/7"
            ],
            "correctOption": "30/41",
            "id": 37
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the derivative of sin(x)?",
            "options": [
                "cos(x)",
                "-sin(x)",
                "-cos(x)",
                "sin(x)"
            ],
            "correctOption": "cos(x)",
            "id": 19
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of cos(0\u00c2\u00b0)?",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "0",
                "-1",
                "0.5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1",
            "id": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "Let the circumcentre of a triangle with vertices A(a, 3), B(b, 5) and C(a, b)... x+y is equal to :",
            "options": [
                "4/7",
                "1/7",
                "8/7",
                "5/7"
            ],
            "correctOption": "4/7",
            "id": 58
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of solutions of sin3x = cos 2x, in the interval (90,180) is :",
            "options": [
                "4",
                "7",
                "3",
                "1"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1",
            "id": 55
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the determinant of a 2x2 matrix [[a, b], [c, d]]?",
            "options": [
                "ad - bc",
                "ab - cd",
                "ac - bd",
                "a + d"
            ],
            "correctOption": "ad - bc",
            "id": 14
        },
        {
            "question": "In a survey of 220 students... m and n respectively be the least and the most number of students who studied all the three subjects. Then m+n is equal to ___________.",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "20",
                "35",
                "50"
            ],
            "correctOption": "45",
            "id": 41
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the area of a circle with radius r?",
            "options": [
                "\u00cf\u20acr^2",
                "2\u00cf\u20acr",
                "\u00cf\u20acr",
                "r^2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "\u00cf\u20acr^2",
            "id": 11
        },
        {
            "question": "The equation y = sinx sin (x + 2) \u2013 sin^2 (x + 1) represents a straight line lying in :",
            "options": [
                "III and IV QUADRANTS",
                "II and IV QUADRANTS",
                "I, III and IV QUADRANTS",
                "II,III and IV QUADRANTS"
            ],
            "correctOption": "III and IV QUADRANTS",
            "id": 53
        },
        {
            "question": "A software company sets up m number of computer systems... then it took 8 more days to finish the assignment. The value of m is equal to:",
            "options": [
                "150",
                "220",
                "135",
                "250"
            ],
            "correctOption": "150",
            "id": 23
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of 3-digit numbers... not divisible by 3 , is equal to ________.",
            "options": [
                "36",
                "37",
                "35",
                "43"
            ],
            "correctOption": "36",
            "id": 28
        },
        {
            "question": "Number of 4-digit numbers that are less than or equal to 2800 and either divisible by 3 or by 11 , is equal to ____________.",
            "options": [
                "990",
                "700",
                "710",
                "430"
            ],
            "correctOption": "710",
            "id": 29
        },
        {
            "question": "A circle is inscribed in an equilateral triangle of side of length 12... then m+n^2 is equal to",
            "options": [
                "900",
                "470",
                "408",
                "488"
            ],
            "correctOption": "408",
            "id": 39
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of solutions of sin3x = cos 2x, in the interval (90,180) is :",
            "options": [
                "4",
                "7",
                "3",
                "1"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1",
            "id": 35
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the quadratic formula?",
            "options": [
                "x = (-b \u00c2\u00b1 \u00e2\u02c6\u0161(b\u00c2\u00b2 - 4ac)) / 2a",
                "x = (b \u00c2\u00b1 \u00e2\u02c6\u0161(b\u00c2\u00b2 - 4ac)) / 2a",
                "x = (-b \u00c2\u00b1 \u00e2\u02c6\u0161(b\u00c2\u00b2 + 4ac)) / 2a",
                "x = (b \u00c2\u00b1 \u00e2\u02c6\u0161(b\u00c2\u00b2 + 4ac)) / 2a"
            ],
            "correctOption": "x = (-b \u00c2\u00b1 \u00e2\u02c6\u0161(b\u00c2\u00b2 - 4ac)) / 2a",
            "id": 8
        },
        {
            "question": "Number of 4-digit numbers that are less than or equal to 2800 and either divisible by 3 or by 11 , is equal to ____________.",
            "options": [
                "990",
                "700",
                "710",
                "430"
            ],
            "correctOption": "710",
            "id": 49
        },
        {
            "question": "Let f(x) be a quadratic polynomial such that f(-2) + f(3) = 0. If one of the roots of f(x) = 0 is 1, then the sum of the roots of f(x) = 0 is equal to:",
            "options": [
                "3",
                "13/3",
                "35/3",
                "11/3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "11/3",
            "id": 50
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of relations... which are reflexive and transitive but not symmetric, is __________.",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "3",
                "5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 24
        },
        {
            "question": "The equation y = sinx sin (x + 2) \u2013 sin^2 (x + 1) represents a straight line lying in :",
            "options": [
                "III and IV QUADRANTS",
                "II and IV QUADRANTS",
                "I, III and IV QUADRANTS",
                "II,III and IV QUADRANTS"
            ],
            "correctOption": "III and IV QUADRANTS",
            "id": 33
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the solution to the equation 2x + 3 = 7?",
            "options": [
                "x = 2",
                "x = 3",
                "x = 4",
                "x = 1"
            ],
            "correctOption": "x = 2",
            "id": 5
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of sin(0\u00c2\u00b0)?",
            "options": [
                "0",
                "1",
                "-1",
                "0.5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "0",
            "id": 17
        },
        {
            "question": "If z = x + iy satisfies |z| - 2 = 0 and |z - i| - |z + 5i| = 0, then :",
            "options": [
                "x+2y+4=0",
                "x+2y-4=0",
                "x-2y+4=0",
                "x-2y-4=0"
            ],
            "correctOption": "x+2y+4=0",
            "id": 46
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of log10(100)?",
            "options": [
                "2",
                "1",
                "10",
                "100"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2",
            "id": 6
        },
        {
            "question": "If sin A + cos A = \u00bd , then 16(sin(2A) + cos(4A) + sin(6A)) is equal to :",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "-23",
                "35",
                "43"
            ],
            "correctOption": "-23",
            "id": 52
        },
        {
            "question": "A circle is inscribed in an equilateral triangle of side of length 12... then m+n^2 is equal to",
            "options": [
                "900",
                "470",
                "408",
                "488"
            ],
            "correctOption": "408",
            "id": 59
        }
    ]
]